Here‘s a staggering statistic.
这里有一个惊人的统计数据。
Scientists have calculated the total amount of plastic ever made: 8.3 billion tonnes.
科学家们计算出了有史以来生产的塑料总量：83亿吨。
Looked at another way, that’s as heavy as 25,000 Empire State Buildings or one billion elephants.
换个角度看，这相当于25000座帝国大厦的重量，或者10亿头大象的重量。
And incredibly, almost all of it has been made in the last 65 years.
令人难以置信的是，几乎所有这些塑料都是在过去65年里生产出来的。
So what‘s the problem?
那么问题出在哪里呢？
Much plastic is in the form of packaging which is used just once and then thrown away.
很多塑料是以包装的形式存在的，这些包装只使用一次就被扔掉了。
According to a major new study from the University of California, 9% of this is recycled, 12% is incinerated and 79% goes to landfill.
根据加利福尼亚大学的一项重要新研究，其中9%的塑料被回收利用，12%被焚烧，79%被填埋到垃圾填埋场。
And because most plastic doesn’t biodegrade, once it‘s in the ground, it stays there.
而且由于大多数塑料不会生物降解，一旦进入地下，就会一直留在那里。
It’s a situation that has led the paper‘s lead author, ecologist Dr Roland Geyer, to say that we are “rapidly heading towards ’Planet Plastic‘”.
这种情况使得该论文的第一作者、生态学家罗兰·盖耶博士表示，我们正“迅速走向‘塑料星球’”。
He believes that there’s already enough waste out there to cover the whole of Argentina.
他认为，现在已经有足够多的塑料垃圾可以覆盖整个阿根廷了。
The team behind this report also estimate that eight million tonnes of plastic waste are escaping into the sea every year.
同时，这份报告背后的研究团队预估，每年有800万吨塑料垃圾流入海洋。
This has generated concern that plastic is entering the food chain, through fish and other sea life which ingest the smaller fragments.
这引发了人们的担忧，担心塑料会通过摄入较小碎片的鱼类和其他海洋生物而进入食物链。
Of course, the reason why there‘s so much plastic around is that it’s an amazingly useful material.
当然，有这么多塑料的原因是它是一种非常有用的材料。
We can‘t get enough of it.
我们对它的需求源源不断。
It’s durable and adaptable, and is used for everything from yoghurt pots to spaceships.
它耐用且适应性强，从酸奶罐到宇宙飞船，各种东西都要用到它。
But it‘s precisely this quality which makes it a problem.
但恰好是这种特性使它成为了一个问题。
The only way to destroy plastic is to heat or burn it - although this has the side effect of harmful emissions.
销毁塑料的唯一方法是加热或燃烧它——尽管这有产生有害排放物的副作用。
So what’s the alternative, other than using less plastic?
那么，除了减少使用塑料之外，还有什么其他办法呢？
Oceanographer Dr Erik van Sebille from Utrecht University says we‘re facing a “tsunami” of plastic waste, and that the global waste industry needs to “get its act together”.
乌得勒支大学的海洋学家埃里克·范·塞比尔博士说，我们正面临着塑料垃圾的“海啸”，全球垃圾处理行业需要“行动起来”。
Professor Richard Thompson, a marine biologist from Plymouth University, says it’s poor design that‘s at fault.
普利茅斯大学的海洋生物学家理查德·汤普森教授说，设计不佳难辞其咎。
He says that if products are currently designed “with recyclability in mind”, they could be recycled around 20 times over.
他说，如果目前的产品在设计时“考虑到可回收性”，它们可以被回收利用大约20次。
Dr Geyer agrees: “The holy grail of recycling is to keep material in use and in the loop for ever if you can.
盖耶博士表示赞同：“回收利用的圣杯就是要尽可能让材料一直被使用并处于循环之中。
But it turns out in our study that actually 90% of that material that did get recycled - which I think we calculated was 600 million tonnes - only got recycled once.”
但我们的研究表明，在我们计算得出约6亿吨的回收材料中，实际上90%的材料只被回收利用了一次而已。”